Jascha Heifetz Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1911-1974 (Box 1-247)
  - Music by Other Composers (Box-folder 15/2-11, Box 16-247)
    - Composers
      - Brahms, Johannes
        - [Concerto, violin, cello, op. 102, A minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 45/3)
        - [Concerto, violin, cello, op. 102, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 45/4-5)
        - [Concerto, violin, cello, op. 102, A minor; arr.], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 45/6)
        - [Intermezzo, op. 76, no. 3], Piano score (Box-folder 45/7)
        - [Intermezzo, op. 117, no. 1, E-flat major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco (Box-folder 46/1)
        - [Intermezzo, op. 118, no. 2, A major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 46/2)
        - Liebeslider Walzer, Piano score (Box-folder 46/3)
        - Six waltzes, 2 piano, 4 hands score (Box-folder 46/4)
        - Neue Liebeslieder Walzer, Piano score (Box-folder 46/5)
        - Wiegenlied, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 46/6)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 25, G minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 46/7)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, no. 2, op. 26, A major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 46/8)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, no. 3, op. 60, C minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 46/9)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, op. 51, no. 1, C minor], Parts (Box-folder 47/1)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 2, op. 51, no. 2, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 47/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 3, op. 67, B-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 47/3)
        - [Quintet, clarinet, strings, op. 115, B minor], Parts (Box-folder 47/4)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, op. 34, F minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 47/5)
        - [Quintet, strings, op. 88, F major], Parts (Box-folder 47/6)
        - [Quintet, strings, op. 111, G major], Parts (Box-folder 47/7)
        - [Quintet, strings, op. 111, G major], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - Sonatensatz (scherzo), Piano score and part (Box-folder 47/8)
        - [Serenade, orchestra, no. 1, op. 11, D major], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Sextet, strings, no. 1, op. 18, B-flat major], Score (Box-folder 47/9)
        - [Sextet, strings, no. 1, op. 18, B-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 48/1)
        - [Sextet, strings, no. 2, op. 36, G major], Parts (Box-folder 48/2)
        - [Sonata, clarinet, piano, no. 1, op. 120, no. 1, F minor; arr.], Piano-viola score and part (Box-folder 48/3)
        - [Sonata, clarinet, piano, no. 2, op. 120, no. 2, E-flat major; arr.], Piano-viola score and part (Box-folder 48/4)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 1, op. 78, G major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 48/5)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 2, op. 100, A major], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 48/6)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, no. 3, op. 1], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 48/7)
        - F.A.E. Sonate, Piano-violin score and part; Collaborative work by Brahms, Albert Dietrich, and Robert Schumann (Box-folder 49/1)
        - [Symphony, no. 1, op. 68, C minor], Miniature score; Various editions (2) (Box 210)
        - [Symphony, no. 2, op. 73, D major], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Symphony, no. 3, op. 90. F major], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Symphony, no. 4, op. 98, E minor], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Symphonies; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 49/2)
        - [Tragische Ouverture, op. 81], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Trio, piano, clarinet, cello, op. 114, A minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 49/3)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 8, B major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 49/4)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, no. 2, op. 87, C major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 49/5)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, no. 3, op. 101, C minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 49/6)
        - [Trio, piano, violin, horn, op. 40, E-flat major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 49/7)
        - [Ungarische Tänze], Piano (4 hands) score; 2 vols. (Box-folder 50/1)
        - Hungarian Dances, Piano (4 hands) score; 2 vols. (Box-folder 50/2)
        - [Ungarische Tänze; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; arr. by Joseph Joachim (Box-folder 50/3)
        - [Ungarische Tänze, no. 1-10; arr.], Piano-violin score only (Box-folder 50/4)
        - [Ungarische Tänze, no. 11-16; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 51/1)
        - [Ungarische Tänze, no. 17-21; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 51/2)
        - [Ungarische Tänze, no. 17; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 51/3)
        - [Variationen über ein Thema von Joseph Haydn, op. 56a], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Variationen über ein Thema von Joseph Haydn, op. 56b], 2 piano, 4 hands score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 51/4)
        - [Waltzes, op. 39], Piano (4 hands) score; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 51/5)
        - [Waltz, op. 39, no. 15, A major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 51/6)
        - Piano works, Volume II, Piano score (Box-folder 51/7)
      - Bridge, Frank
        - 3 Idylls for string quartet, Parts (Box-folder 52/1)
      - Britten, Benjamin
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 15; arr.] See also: correspondence with Britten which includes notes on this work, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 52/2)
      - Brown, Eddy
        - Rondino on a melody by J.B. Cramer, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 52/3)
      - Bruch, Max
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 26, G minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 52/4)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 26, G minor], Parts (Box-folder 52/5-7)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 1, op. 26, G minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 52/8)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 44, D minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 53/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 44, D minor], Parts (Box-folder 53/2-4)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 2, op. 44, D minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 53/5)
        - [Fantasie unter freier Benutzung Schottischer Volksmelodien, violin, orchestra, op. 46], Orchestral score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 54/1)
        - [Fantasie unter freier Benutzung Schottischer Volksmelodien, violin, orchestra, op. 46], Parts (Box-folder 54/2-5)
        - [Fantasie unter freier Benutzung Schottischer Volksmelodien, violin, orchestra, op. 46; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 54/6)
        - [Romanze, violin, orchestra, op. 42; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 55/1)
        - [Romanze, violin, orchestra, op. 42; arr.], Photostat and negative photostat of piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 55/1)
      - Bruckner, Anton
        - [Quintet, strings], Parts (Box-folder 55/2)
      - Bull, Ole
        - Polacca Guerrica, Piano-violin score (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Burgin, Richard
        - [Scales], Holograph violin score; Laid in: letter (Box-folder 55/4)
      - Burleigh, Cecil
        - Giant Hills, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 55/5)
        - Moto perpetuo, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 55/6)
        - Tints, op. 38, no. 3, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 55/7)
      - Burmester, Willy
        - Französisches lied, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 55/8)
      - Carmichael, Hoagy
        - Stardust, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 55/9)
      - Carpenter, John Alden
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Photostat of holograph [?] piano-violin score (Box-folder 55/10)
      - Casella, Alfredo
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 62], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 56/1)
      - Castelnuovo-Tedesco, Mario
        - [Alt Wien, op. 30; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 56/2)
        - Arise, Holograph violin score (Box-folder 56/3)
        - [La bisbetica domata. Overture], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Capitan Francassa, op. 16], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 56/4)
        - [Chant Hébraïque, op. 39; arr.], Holograph piano-cello score and violin part (Box-folder 56/5)
        - [Chant Hébraïque, op. 39; arr.], Printed paino-violin score and part (Box-folder 56/5)
        - Cherubino: two arias from "the marriage of Figaro" freely transcribed by Castenuovo-Tedeso (Box-folder 56/6)
        - [Concerto, cello, op. 72], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Concerto, cello, op. 72; arr.], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 56/7)
        - Allegretto gentile, Holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 56/8)
        - Concerto Italiano, Holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 56/9)
        - Concerto Italiano, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 56/10)
        - I profeti, Holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 57/1)
        - I profeti, Ms. orchestral score (Box-folder 57/2)
        - I profeti, Negative photostat of orchestral score, p. 1-75 (Box-folder 57/3)
        - I profeti, Negative photostat of orchestral score, p. 76-170 (Box-folder 57/4)
        - I profeti, Negative photostat of orchestral score, p. 171-255 (Box-folder 58/1)
        - I profeti, Reverse photostat of orchestral score, p. 1-127 (Box-folder 58/2)
        - I profeti, Reverse photostat of orchestral score, p. 128-255 (Box-folder 58/3)
        - I profeti, Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 58/4)
        - I profeti, Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 58/5)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, op. 102], Holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 59/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, no. 3, op. 102], Holograph piano-violin score of movements I and III; marked "2nd version" (Box-folder 59/2)
        - [Divertimento, violin, viola], Photostat of holograph violin-viola score (Box-folder 59/3)
        - [Figaro!, violin, orchestra], Photostat of holograph orchestral score (Box-folder 242/5)
        - [Figaro!, violin, orchestra], Parts (Box-folder 59/4-7)
        - [Figaro!, violin, piano], Ozalid of piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 60/1)
        - Serenatella (on the name of Jascha Heifetz), Photostat of holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 60/2)
        - Hungarian serenade (on the name of Miklos Rosza), Photostat of piano-violin score (Box-folder 60/3)
        - The lark: poem for violin and piano, Holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 60/4)
        - The lark: poem for violin and piano, Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 60/5)
        - Lo, the messiah, Piano-SATB score (Box-folder 60/6)
        - [I Nottambuli, op. 47], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 60/7)
        - [Notturno adriatico, op. 54], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 60/8)
        - [Notturno e tarentella], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 60/9)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 1, op. 58, G major], Parts (Box-folder 60/10)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 69], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 60/11)
        - [Passetempi, op. 58], Piano score (Box-folder 60/12)
        - [Ritmi, op. 15], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 61/1)
        - Rome express, Holograph violin score (Box-folder 61/2)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, no. 1, op. 49, G major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 61/3)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, no. 2, op. 70], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 61/4)
        - Valse, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 61/5)
        - Tre vocalizzi, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 61/6)
      - Catoire, Georgi
        - Poeme: zweite Sonate, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 61/7)
      - Chabrier, Emmanuel
        - Bourrée fantasque, Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 61/8)
      - Chadwick, George Whitefield
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 4, E minor], Parts (Box-folder 61/9)
      - Chaminade, Cecile
        - [Serenade espagnole; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 61/10)
      - Chausson, Ernest
        - Chanson perpétuelle, op. 37, Piano-voice-string quartet score (2) and parts (Box-folder 61/11)
        - [Concert, piano, violin, string quartet, op. 21, D minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 62/1)
        - [Poème, violin, orchestra, op. 25], Orchestral score (Box-folder 62/2)
        - [Poème, violin, orchestra, op. 25], Parts (Box-folder 62/3-4)
        - [Quartet, piano,strings, op. 30, A major], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 63/1)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 35], Parts (Box-folder 63/2)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 3, G minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 63/3)
      - Cherubini, Luigi
        - [Quartets, strings, no. 1-3], Parts (Box-folder 63/4)
      - Chopin, Frédéric
        - [Etudes, piano; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 63/5)
        - [Lithauisches lied; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 64/1)
        - [Mazurkas, piano; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 64/2)
        - [Mazurka, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 64/3)
        - [Nocturnes, piano], Piano score (Box-folder 64/4)
        - [Nocturne, piano, C-sharp minor], Piano score; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 64/5)
        - [Nocturne, piano, C-sharp minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Nathan Milstein (Box-folder 64/6)
        - [Nocturne, op. 9, no. 2; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (2); Arranged by Pablo Sarasate (Box-folder 64/7)
        - [Nocturne, op. 27, no. 2; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (3); Arranged by August Wilhelmj (Box-folder 64/8)
        - [Nocturne, op. 72, E minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 64/9)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 8, G minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 64/10)
        - [Waltzes, no. 1-15], Piano score (Box-folder 65/1)
        - [Waltz, op. 70, no. 1, G-flat major; arr.], Violin part only; Arranged by Albert Spalding (Box-folder 65/2)
        - Album for the piano, Piano score (Box-folder 65/3)
      - Clementi, Muzio
        - [Sonatas, piano. Selections], Piano score (Box-folder 65/4)
      - Clérambault, Louis Nicolas
        - Largo, Piano-violin score and part (2) (Box-folder 65/5)
      - Cobilovici, Émile
        - Tableaux synoptiques des sons harmoniques du violon (Box-folder 65/6)
      - Cohen, Alexander
        - Extracts from co-ordinative exercises, Holograph violin score (Box-folder 65/7)
      - Confrey, Zez
        - Novelty piano solos, Piano score (Box-folder 65/8)
      - Conus, Julius
        - Sept caprices rhythmiques, Holograph piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 65/9)
        - [Concerto, violin], Orchestral score (Box-folder 65/10)
        - [Concerto, violin], Photostat of above (Box-folder 66/1)
        - [Concerto, violin], Negative photostat of orchestral score (Box-folder 66/2)
        - [Concerto, violin], Parts (Box-folder 66/3-4)
        - [Concerto, violin], Reverse photstats of string parts (Box-folder 67/1)
        - [Concerto, violin], Negative photostat of string parts (Box-folder 67/2)
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (3) (Box-folder 67/3)
      - Copland, Aaron
        - Waltz and celebration, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 67/4)
      - Corelli, Arcangelo
        - Follies d'espagne, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 67/5)
        - La folia, Piano-violin score and part; edited by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 67/6)
      - Coslow, Sam
        - Carnegie hall, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 67/7)
      - Cottenet, R.
        - Chanson-meditation, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 67/8)
      - Couperin, François
        - [Les petits moulins à vent; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 68/1)
      - Coward, Noël
        - I'll see you again, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 68/2)
      - Crowther, John
        - Gweedore brae, Holograph piano-violin score (Box-folder 68/3)
        - Gweedore brae, Printed piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 68/3)
      - Cui, César
        - Orientale, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 68/4)
        - Berceuse, Piano-violin score and part; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 68/5)
        - [Suite concertante, op. 25, no. 1], Violin-piano score and part (Box-folder 68/6)
      - Daquin, Claude
        - Le coucou, Piano score (Box-folder 68/7)
        - [Le Coucou; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 68/8)
      - Debausky, Louis
        - [Studies for violin, op. 1, pt. 1], Violin exercise book (Box-folder 68/9)
      - Debussy, Claude
        - Children's corner, Piano score (Box-folder 68/10)
        - Le petit berger, Piano score (Box-folder 68/11)
        - [Danse; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 68/12)
        - [L'Enfant prodigue; arr.] (Box-folder 68/13)
        - [Pelléas et Mélisande. La mort de Pelléas; arr.], Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 68/14)
        - Petite suite, Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 68/15)
        - En bateau, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 69/1)
        - [La plus que lente; arr.], 4 hands piano score (Box-folder 69/2)
        - [La plus que lente; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; 2nd copy, violin part only (Box-folder 69/3)
        - Préludes (1er livre), Piano score (Box-folder 69/4)
        - Le fille aux cheveux de lin, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 69/5)
        - [Quartet, strings, op. 10], Parts (Box-folder 69/6)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 69/7)
        - Clair de lune, Piano-violin score and parts (Box-folder 69/8)
        - 43 songs for voice and piano (high), Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 69/9)
      - Delibes, Leo
        - L'Escapolette, 4 hands piano score (Box-folder 70/1)
      - Delius, Frederick
        - [Concerto, violin; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 70/2)
      - Destouches, André Cardinal
        - [Passepied; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 70/3)
      - Dittersdorf, Carl
        - [Quartet, strings, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 70/4)
      - Dobrowen, Issay
        - Fable, Piano-violin score and part; (2) (Box-folder 70/5)
      - Dohnányi, Ernst von
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 2, op. 15, D-flat major], Parts; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 70/6)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 3, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 70/7)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, op. 1, C minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 70/8)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, #2, op. 26, E-flat minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 70/9)
        - [Ruralia Hungarica, op. 32], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 70/10)
        - [Ruralia Hungarica, orchestra, op. 32b], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Serenade, string trio, op. 10], Parts (Box-folder 70/11)
        - [Sonata, violin, piano, op. 21], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 71/1)
      - Donato, Anthony
        - [Quartet, strings, E minor], Score (Box-folder 71/2)
      - Dont, Jacob
        - Etudes, op. 35, Violin score (Box-folder 71/3)
        - Etincelles, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 71/4)
      - Dounis, Demetrius
        - The absolute independence of the fingers, Violin score; 2 vols. (Box-folder 71/5)
        - Die Künstlertechnik des Violinspiels, Violin score (Box-folder 71/6)
      - Drdla, Franz
        - Souvenir, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 71/7)
      - Drigo, Ricardo
        - [Valse bluette; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; 2nd copy, violin part only; Arr. by Leopold Auer (Box-folder 71/8)
      - Dubensky, Arcady
        - Fugue for nine stands of 1st violin section, Miniature score (Box 210)
        - Gossips (les commérages), Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 71/9)
      - Dvořák, Antonin
        - [Concerto, cello, op. 104, B minor; arr.], Piano-cello score and part (Box-folder 72/1)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 53, A minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 72/2)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 53, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 72/3-4)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 53, A minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 72/5)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, op. 87, E-flat major], Piano score and part (Box-folder 72/6)
        - [Quartet, piano, strings, op. 87, E-flat major], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 7, op. 16, A minor], Parts (Box-folder 73/1)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 10, op. 51, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 73/2)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 11, op. 61, C major], Parts (Box-folder 73/3)
        - [Quartet, strings, no 8, op. 80, E major], Parts (Box-folder 73/4)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 12, op. 96, F major], Parts (Box-folder 73/5)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 14, op. 105, A-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 73/6)
        - [Quartet, strings, no. 13, op. 106, G major], Parts (Box-folder 73/7)
        - [Quartets, strings. Selections], Miniature (Box 210)
        - [Quintet, piano, strings, op. 81, A major], Piano score and parts; Various editions (2) (Box-folder 74/1)
        - [Quintet, strings, op. 77, G major], Parts (Box-folder 74/2)
        - [Quintet, strings, op. 97, E-flat major], Parts (Box-folder 74/3)
        - [Romantische stücke, op. 75], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 74/4)
        - [Sextet, strings, op. 48, A major], Parts (Box-folder 74/5)
        - Slavonic dances, op. 46, Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 74/6)
        - Slavonic dances, op. 72, Piano (4 hands) score (Box-folder 74/7)
        - [Slavonic dance, op. 72, no. 1, B major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 74/8)
        - [Slavonic dance, op. 72, no. 2, E minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 74/9)
        - [Slavonic dance, op. 72, no. 8, A-flat major; arr.], Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 75/1)
        - Indian lament, Piano-violin score and part; Arranged by Fritz Kreisler (Box-folder 75/2)
        - [Symphony, no. 9, op. 95, E minor], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Terzetto, op. 74], Violin (2) and viola parts (Box-folder 75/3)
        - [Trio, piano, strings, op. 65, F minor], Piano score and parts (Box-folder 75/4)
        - Dumky-Trio, Piano score and parts (Box-folder 75/5)
        - Ziguenermelodien, op. 55, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 75/6)
      - Dyer, Susan
        - An outlandish suite, Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 75/7)
      - Elgar, Edward
        - [La capricieuse, op. 17], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 75/8)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 61, B minor], Orchestral score (Box-folder 75/9)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 61, B minor], Parts (Box-folder 76/1-5, Box-folder 77/1-2)
        - [Concerto, violin, op. 61, B minor; arr.], Piano-violin score and part (Box-folder 77/3)
        - Etudes caractéristiques, op. 24, Violin score (Box-folder 77/4)
        - Exercise for the 3rd finger, Holograph violin score; copied by the composer from the original; Inscribed: Written Oct 7:1878 for my own use & copied for Mr. Jascha Heifetz at his kind request and offered to him with great admiration/Edward Elgar/Nov:20:1920 (Box-folder 77/5)
        - Exercise for the 3rd finger, Negative photostat of above (Box-folder 77/5)
      - Ellington, Edward (Duke)
        - [Solitude; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 78/1)
        - Sophisticated lady, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 78/2)
      - Elman, Mischa
        - Favorite encores, Piano-violin score and part; Edited by Mischa Elman (Box-folder 78/3)
      - Endicott, Samuel
        - When silence falls, Piano-vocal score (Box-folder 78/4)
      - Enesco, Georges
        - [Roumanian rhapsody, no. 1, op. 11, A major], Miniature score (Box 210)
        - [Roumanian rhapsody, no. 1, op. 11, no. 1, A major; arr.], Piano score (Box-folder 78/5)